ABHIJIT HANUMANT JADHAV

abhijit.jadhav1998@gmail.com

🕻 +91 8446755971 Pune, Maharashtra, India









CAREER SUMMARY

1.6+ years of full-stack development experience as a Java Developer in analysis, design, implementation, integration, testing, and maintenance of applications using Java. Extensively worked on ERP with good knowledge of developing complex projects and good management skills of the deliverables.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Accenture - Application Development Analyst December 2021 To Present (1.6 Year)

- · Working on agile scrum methodology and involved in standup meetings to monitor the progress.
- Involved in requirement gathering, analysis, design, optimization, and documentation of the application.
- Implementing full-stack application using Spring boot, Spring MVC, Spring Security, Spring Data JPA, and Web services.
- Writing various Junit test cases for Unit Testing.
- Time Entry workflow optimization on ERP.
- Worked on Inactive user Automation and PS Level Restriction Automation on ERP.
- Member of MyExperience team responsible for arranging Team building events at DU Level.

INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE

Persistent Systems - Software Engineer Intern January 2019 To June 2019 (6 Months)

- Interview Automation on an online campus test conducting platform called CodeSlash.
- Integrated the automation module with the application enabling the feature of conducting the interview on the platform. Developed the workflow of the Admin side, User side, and evaluator side.
- Performed the integration and unit testing of the application on the staging platform further the application was deployed on the production server. implementing best practices.

OPEN SOURCE CONTRIBUTIONS

- Contributor to cartoonizer web Deep learning application.
- Technical blogger at Medium.
- Content writer at GeekforGeeks.
- Published "Deepfake Video Detection using Neural Networks", International Journal for Scientific Research and Development,04 April 2020

SKILLS

FRONT END

React, HTML, CSS, JavaScript

BACK END

Java, SpringBoot, Microservice, Python for AI

DATABASE

MYSOL

UNIT TESTING

JUnit, Mockito Framework

DEVOPS

Docker, Kubernetes

OTHERS

Deep Learning, Data Structures and Algorithms

PROJECT

- DeepFake Video Detection
- AI-Based Attendance System
- Railway Reservation System

CERTIFICATIONS

- Master Microservices with Spring Boot By
- Master Java Unit Testing with Spring Boot & Mockito By Udemy.
- Deep Learning Specialization from deeplearning.ai on Coursera
- Infosys Certified Software Programmer through InfyTQ

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Boards of Studies Member at G. H. Raisoni College of Engineering and Management, Pune
- 1st Rank Second Year, Third Year, Fourth Year in B.Tech

EDUCATION

- B.Tech | Computer Engineering | CGPA: 9.19 | G. H Raisoni College of Engineering and Management, Pune (2016 - 2020)
- AISSCE | Percentage: 62.2% | Army Public School, Kirkee (March 2016)
- AISSE | CGPA: 9.19 | JArmy Public School, Chandimandir (March 2014)